{"data":[{"question":"That is the best book that I ________ on that subject.","a":"had read","b":"read","c":"have read","d":"am reading","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: You can use the Present Perfect to describe your experience (the first\/the most...that...).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Yesterday I met the woman who ________ us with the work next month.","a":"will help","b":"helps","c":"has helped","d":"is helping","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple Future tense (next month).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"That ________ the best movie that I had seen for a long time.","a":"will be","b":"has been","c":"is","d":"was","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense: expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past- first clause should be simple past tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"He said that he ________ me there at 4.30 this afternoon.","a":"would meet","b":"met","c":"will meet","d":"meets","answer":"1","explain":"\n- In reported speech: \n+ If the reporting verb (i.e. said) is in the past, the reported clause will be in a past form. This form is usually one step back into the past from the original. \n+ If simple present, present perfect or the future is used in the reporting verb (i.e. says) the tense is retained.\u00a0\n+ If reporting a general truth the present tense will be retained or even the future tense can be used.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Maxwell ________ three dollars for the tie he bought at Macy's.","a":"had paid","b":"paid","c":"pays","d":"would pay","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Bought: shows that this is simple past tense- .... is simple past tense, too.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The salesman was telling me that he ________ ten cars last week.","a":"sold","b":"had sold","c":"would sell","d":"has sold","answer":"2","explain":"\n- In reported speech: \n+ If the reporting verb (i.e. said) is in the past, the reported clause will be in a past form. This form is usually one step back into the past from the original. \n+ If simple present, present perfect or the future is used in the reporting verb (i.e. says) the tense is retained.\u00a0\n+ If reporting a general truth the present tense will be retained or even the future tense can be used.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Did Bob say that he ________ from Princeton in 1951?","a":"would graduate","b":"graduates","c":"has graduated","d":"had graduated","answer":"4","explain":"\n- In reported speech: \n+ If the reporting verb (i.e. said) is in the past, the reported clause will be in a past form. This form is usually one step back into the past from the original. \n+ If simple present, present perfect or the future is used in the reporting verb (i.e. says) the tense is retained.\u00a0\n+ If reporting a general truth the present tense will be retained or even the future tense can be used.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"We bought a used car that had belonged to an old couple who used the car only when they ________ shopping.","a":"go","b":"went","c":"are going","d":"has gone","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Used: shows that this is simple past tense- .... is simple past tense, too.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The man who will replace Mr. Stuart ________ yesterday.","a":"arrives","b":"will arrive","c":"arrived","d":"has arrived","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple Past tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (yesterday).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"We thought that they ________ to Arizona yesterday.","a":"would move","b":"moved","c":"will move","d":"had moved","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (yesterday).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"}]}